BEMISTER TESSEMA

GAME DEVELOPER

Passion isn't enough to get someone through the arduous grind that game development presents. Thats when discipline and dedication to the craft comes into play. My dedication is complimented perfectly by my expertise in Unity 3D and C# programing

EXPERIENCES:

Math and Science Tutor

09/2016 - 03 2018

Contra Costa College - San Pablo, CA

- Tutored high-school math students on everything from basic Algebra to Calculus.
- Used positive reinforcement, repetition, and review to help students master challenging material.

JYSEP Program Coordinator

08/2017 - 10/2018

JYSEP - San Pablo, CA

- Hosted an afterschool study program for youth in local Elementary Schools.
- Assisted students in completing homework assignments and studying ahead.

Teacher's Assistant

09/2015 - 07 2017

St. Callistus Church - El Sobrante, CA

- Assisted lead teacher with lesson plan creation and material development.
- Oversaw students in classrooms and common areas to monitor, enforce rules, and support teachers.

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Science - Game Design

10/2020 - 06/2022

University of California, Santa Cruz - Santa Cruz, CA

 Relevant Coursework: Game Design, Game Al, Game Technologies, Advanced Programming

Associates in Liberal Arts - Math and Science

08/2014 - 06/2018

Contra Costa College - San Pablo, CA

· Graduated with both my Associate's degree and a high school diploma.

High School Diploma

08/2014 - 06/2018

Middle College High School - San Pablo, CA

• Attended college classes concurrently with my high school courses.

CONTACT

510-255-2510 Bemi080@gmail.com 1322 Redwood Circle, San Pablo, CA

SKILLS:

- · Leadership and Teamwork
- Unity 3D
- · C# Programming
- · Git Version Control
- · Blender 3D
- Adobe Photoshop

LANGUAGES:

- English
- Amharic